tmcgalleries.com 2018-05-17

# 18magazine.com Privacy Policy

**On This Page:**

  * [Where to Direct Questions About 18magazine.com's Privacy Policy](http://www.panchodog.com/privacy.php?tsite=18magazine.com#privacy-policy)

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. 

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how 18magazine.com collects information from all end users of 18magazine.com's Internet services (the "Services") those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Service ("Members") what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. 18magazine.com requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**Personal Information 18magazine.com Collects and How It Is Used**

**Introduction.** 18magazine.com collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our Service. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below. 

**Registration**. Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. However, in instances where 18magazine.com and a partner jointly promote the Services, 18magazine.com may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address, and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. 18magazine.com may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members). As explained in more detail below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on the Services. 

**18magazine.com Partners and Sponsors.** Some 18magazine.com products and services are offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with a non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Members some of these products and services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In these instances, you will be notified before any such data is collected or transferred and may decide not to use that particular service or feature. 

**Online Shopping.** At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a services or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information. 

If you order products directly from 18magazine.com, we will use the personal information you provide only to process that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

**Online Advertisements.** 18magazine.com displays our online advertisements. We share aggregated and non-identifying information about our Visitors and Members collected through the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers. Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. For instance, an advertiser tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display the advertisement to the intended audience. 18magazine.com does not share personal information about its Visitors or Members with these advertisers. 

**Responses to Email Inquiries**. When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to 18magazine.com, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. 18magazine.com does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. 

**Voluntary Customer Surveys**. We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary. 

We take the information we receive from individuals responding to our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other 18magazine.com customers to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties. 

**Special Cases.** It is 18magazine.com's policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. However, 18magazine.com may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect 18magazine.com and our Members. 

**"Cookies" and How 18magazine.com Uses Them**. A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. 18magazine.com may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your session settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-18magazine.com Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. 

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them. 

**18magazine.com's Commitment to Children's Privacy.** Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. While we do not anticipate a particular need, it is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws where applicable. 

**Public Forums.** Please remember that any information you may disclose in public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

**18magazine.com's Commitment to Data Security**. Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. 

**How to Access or Modify Your Information.** 18magazine.com offers Members the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration. To access or modify such information, contact our Customer Service Department at [support@18magazine.com ](mailto:support@18magazine.com). 

**Where to Direct Questions About 18magazine.com's Privacy Policy.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact: 

Customer Service   
18magazine.com 

**Revisions to This Policy.** 18magazine.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Affiliate Terms of Service and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted in accordance with the on this Web site.
